welcome to category five technology TV
gratam genus technology quinque TV
this is episode number 573 and tonight's
Hic est numerus DLXXIII res ac nocte scriptor
a show we've got a great show planned
et cogitavit spectaculum magnus ostendit Comperto
first of all we've been talking a little
Primus omnium loquentes weve 'been paulum
bit about fake SD cards we're gonna put
SD pecto ut aliquantulus fake de posito amet
them to the test we're gonna see tonight
ut nos probati pareamus amet nocte videre
if they're real and on top of that we're
ac si verus es super illo sumus
going to take a quick look at Linux Mint
Linux Mint velox inviso ventura
don't go anywhere we've got a great show
Comperto non egredieris inde huc magnum spectaculum
this is category 5 technology TV
Hoc genus technology V TV
[Music]
[Musica]
our live recordings are trusted only to
Vivamus solum confidebat sunt tabulas scripto nostro
solid-state drives by Kingston
solidum-statu agat in Kingeston '
technology revive your computer with
cum computatrum technology vivifica tui
improved performance and reliability
et meliorem reliability
over traditional hard drives with
per limitem agit durum traditional
Kingston SSDs category 5 TV streams live
V vivunt TV rivos genus Kingeston 'SSDs
with Telestream Wirecast and nimble
de Aeris inmensi superat Telestream Wirecast
streamer tune in every week on roku Kodi
tune in streamer in omni septimana roku Kodi
flex and other HLS video players the
LENTO et alia histriones in HLS video
local show times visit category 5 TV
ostende tempora, loci V visita genus TV
category 5 TV is a member of the tech
V genus TV est membrum in tech
podcast network if it's tech it's here
Mass si suus 'network tech suus' hic
cat 5 TV slash TPN and the international
V cattus TV VULNUS TPN et gentium
association of internet broadcasters cat
consociatione penitus broadcasters cattus
5 TV slash iai be welcome to category 5
V TV VULNUS iai suscipe V genus
technology TV it's so great to see you
TV technology illud tanto te videre
again this week I'm Robby Ferguson I am
Hoc septimana item Tacitus Robby ego sum
Sasha Rickman and this week we've got a
Comperto a week et Sasha Rickman
fantastic show planned for you as I
cogitavit enim sicut ostendunt fantastic
mentioned at the top of the show we're
de quibus ante sumus top of spectaculum
gonna be looking at fake SD cards we're
'agnus dei esse a respiciens fake SD pecto sumus
gonna be looking at another Linux distro
sit amet vultus modo Linux distraho
that looks strikingly similar to the one
spectat insignite simile
that we've already looked at how strange
ut weve 'iam novis, quam intuens
is that
quod
I know I know great to see you chat room
Scio scio te chat cubiculum ut magna
everybody joining us nice to see ya
bellum ut veniendo omnibus ya videre
thanks to all of our ops who are helping
qui auxilio gratiae ad nostrae Opis
keep things clean and we appreciate you
ut non rogemus res pollutum et mundum
very very much
diversi generis multa nimis valde
hey I saw that I've been promoted people
heus vidi quod populus Ego promotus
have just been getting kicked for saying
Iustus questus est et ait in calce
hello I mean this is we really did not
non enim re vera non sit haec salve
use appropriate emoticon yeah I call
yeah voco uti oportet emoticon
them emoticons they're emojis I'm here
tu me hic non emoticons eos emojis
in IC q how come it's not going oh oh
Q suus 'non iens ut adveho in IC oh oh
that's weird
quod est cerritulus
we should do that we should hook up our
faciamus nobis camur nostrum
chat room to make the ice I now want
nunc glacies locus enim vis ad chat
that to be my dad Greg did you know that
ut et tu nosti quia meum dad Greg
my wife and I met on AIESEC you I did
AIESEC est uxor mea et ego non sum occurrit
know that that's how we met that makes
scimus enim quod facit illud ut conveniremus
me happy yeah like the old days of
yeah beatam mei sicut diebus antiquis
Internet chat IRC Internet Relay Chat I
Internet chat Internet Nullam Chat ut IRC
met David a regular like out a bar at a
David autem bar ad exire ut convenerat a ordinarius
bar yeah I where's like the bar of geek
ubi yeah non excludit a talea ut geek
exactly yeah essentially that's exactly
yeah prorsus se prorsus ut '
what I CQ was what's funny is so it took
Kessinger quod erat tulit eam quae tam iocularis
not to bring it back to me and all of
ut reduces me omnes
the time but Dave ordered a salad and an
Dave sed tempus iubet et ACETARIA
iced tea at a wing bar that I worked at
PRAESTRICTUS tea vectes, qui ad cornu ad laboravi
and he was trying to impress he had my
et est qui quaerit et meam impress
full attention immediately I'm like a
attendentes quasi statim plenus sum
salad this guy
Hoc ACETARIA Guido
anyway it's like that yeah
usquam suus 'amo ut yeah
it's like 9 p.m. what's what are you
IX suus 'non ut suus' Quid autem tu es enim post meridiem
doing it's like the last ice day
facit similis ultimum diem glaciei
incidentally ICQ actually still exists
per accidens etiam existit in actu AIM
can you believe it doesn't know I mean
non credis quia non sum mean
as much as Tom and MySpace still exists
Tom est quod adhuc exstat et MySpace
but it's there it still is in operation
verum est quod adhuc sunt in operationem
the server's still how many people are
tamen quot sunt a servo suus '
on it I don't know I mean I know that I
super illud nescio intelliguntur Ego scio me
am to 1 4 8 4 6 3 2 your vows but it
I IV VI III IV VIII ad II sum, sed non voto fertiliora tuo
could have been that's the priest is at
quod ingressus sacerdos viderit reversam esse potuit ad
the front 2 1 4 8 4 6 3 - do you take
II fronte I IV VI III IV VIII - tolle tibi
Becca Ferguson as your Becca Smith as
Becca tua Becca Smith, ut Tacitus
your lawfully wedded wife I CQ something
CQ ipsis legitimis me aliquid uxor tua
like that yeah nobody seriously does
yeah, quod nullus non, sicut gravissime
still exist I've logged in and it's
Ego adhuc est, et initium est
there we here does that and people are
Hic et ibi habet, qui sunt
like what is this thing that you're
quid est hoc, quod aliquid simile es
talking about they still make it
tamen de hoc faciunt
they still make it I love it huge back
eam tamen amo illud dorsum immane
in the day that was like the Facebook
quasi Cornelius diem
right when Facebook was popular I I
cum popularibus esse iure Facebook II
remember like nobody had computers at
memini sicut computers nullus habuit apud
their house or at least my family didn't
vel saltem domo mea non fecistis
and we went like I would have to go to
quod nos volo ut ire
the computer lab at the school and there
Lab computer quod in ludo est
were only like I think yeah yeah
in tantum ut yeah yeah puto
designation I don't remember mine
Non memini vocabulo mea
there was like 12 computers in this
XII, sicut est in computers
computer lab I feel like nobody had a
nullus erat ut sentio computatrum Lab
computer at home and I was like one of
computatrum in domo esset et sicut unus ex
four people ever in there like it was so
ita semper quasi quattuor hominibus
not a big deal that I always really
et non pensi habebat ut semper realiter
appreciate that you judge everyone based
ut omnes bene iudicare secundum
on what you had at home at the time yeah
memini domi habuisti in quo
like nobody had computer nobody a
ut nullus habuit computatrum nullus vir
computer I didn't exactly also nobody
et quoque prorsus non computatrum neminem
had a microwave right cable TV watch TV
Proin vigilo TV a dextris kabeļtelevīzija
on Fridays there you go thanks mom
sexta feria ieiunare non vos mom agentes
I had three computers at the time
Et ego habui tria computers de tempus
whatever back in those days right how
si quid juris in dies
you got a wife see I exactly
prorsus non videre uxorem et got
I stayed single until last year that's
Est usque ad unum annum et mansi
what happened it's because you didn't
quia non est factum
have I seek you that's why this is this
quaero enim quid sit quod
is how things come about so you had to
quam ut ad eveniunt
wait for the guy who was
Qui exspectat amet
during salad and iced tea at the bar
et in PRAESTRICTUS tea per ACETARIA talea
which works it worked Ali I worked out
Ali laboraverunt operatur ea quae ex laboravi
here you are a year later
huc autem post anni
congratulations on the anniversary gave
gratulatus et anniversaria
congratulations well done sir
Euge bone gratulatione
okay we're gonna get into it first of
'agnus dei adepto erant' okay in hoc prima
all we have had an incredible week here
omnes nos qui hic infinitam sabbati
category 5 TV it's been so encouraging
genus V ita fuerit TV suus deprecantes
thank you community for coming together
civitatem gratias ago tibi, quia veniens una
and supporting category 5 TV we've had
et sustentans V genus TV weve 'had
various needs such as our need to be
opus est, ut necessitates nostras variis
able to record category 5 technology TV
potuit V genus technology recordarentur TV
right this is kind of a good thing when
est quoddam bonum et aequum
you run an internet-based TV show to
tu currunt TV show est fundatur in Penitus,
actually actually write so that you can
actually actually scribo ut non potestis
then upload it to the interwebs and to
et deinde fasciculos ad interwebs
our various distribution chain unlike
distribution torquem variis nostra dissimilis
the short list of things you need to be
in brevi rerum vos postulo ut album
able to do it kinda is at the top of the
ut pius non possit facere a summo ad
list yeah number one right so one of our
Yeah justum numerum nostrum album
viewers contributed an Atomos ninja
viewers operam ad Atomos ninja
flame which is a 4k recording device and
recording fabrica 4k, quae est flamma, et
i see it actually flashing right now so
ego animadverto is etiam nunc igitur ecce coruscantes
this is being recorded on the Atomos
quo memoratur in Atomos
ninja flame also we had Michael who
ninja flamma habuimus et cui Michael
donated a LED light bulb which is
in qua donatus duxerunt lux bulbus
blinding me right now it's fantastic
nunc oblito dimisit suus 'fantastic mea
yeah I don't know if you can tell
Nescio si possis dicere yeah
because you probably want sunglasses on
quia vos probabiliter volunt oculariorum solariorum
before you look into the Sun the one in
ante solem intueri unum
the middle
medium
yeah the LED and it is way brighter than
yeah, et duxerunt illum in visu clarior est ita
the rest of the rest of them if you
si reliqua reliquis
squint your eyes actually ended up being
denique quod etiam oculi squint
brighter which I would consider is
hoc est quod considerans splendens procedit
better in an environment it's brighter
in environment est quod melius nitent
and and you know it's a really nice
et nescit quod suus 'a vere nice quod
white light turned out that it's
album enim est lucis convertit manum
brighter than the other bulbs so in
in aliis lucidiora bulbis
Candela D versus fluorescent I'm quite
Candela D versus sum satis fluorescent
impressed that the LED is doing a better
quod melius ducitur imprimi facere
job
officium
music well just like an on-the-fly
sicut etiam super-the-musica esse volant
review of it it actually is amazing
recensionem actu sub ea continetur miris ex eo
there you go there's our on-the-fly
non est enim vos nostra, in-the-volant
review and it is brighter than the
et quod multo plus lucidiores super review
fluorescence and I looked at it and now
Sambucus nunc et intuens
I cannot see the teleprompter so I don't
Teleprompter videre non possum sic facio
know what to say I have no idea where I
Non habeo quid dicam nescio unde sint I
am or what I'm doing but I see how it's
agam et ego non video quomodo aut quid suus '
like I I have gotten into your brain
II tui sicut effectus in cerebrum
feels like to be Sasha the best thing I
Not optimum est quod sentit sicut ex me
do is just I just nodded smile and that
quia iustus est sicut et nutu et risu
I know I wait for a pause
Scio ego exspectabo est mora
oh yeah the other thing that we're
O res aliis, ut sis yeah
working on is
super hoc opus
getting a replacement unit for the XLR
questus a replacement pro unitatis XLR
for your microphone right so that we can
propter quod iure possumus tortor ligula, facilisis
welcome Jeff back and we hope to do that
Gaius suscipit et speramus facere
within the next six months right I mean
tribus proximis mensibus ius voco
it would be nice to have the guy here he
hic esset nice quod amet
misses us and we actually he's here it's
Et hinc est quod suus 'vere et sincere nos
just that we locked him outside right so
clausum est quod foris justum
it would be really nice to be able to
re vera esset nice poterit
let him in to the building and plug in a
plug in eo ut aedes
microphone and that would be really good
et tortor ligula, facilisis realiter esset bonum
he's gonna have so much to say but it's
sed dico suus 'agnus dei se habet ad multa, sic suus'
having on he'll be like I've been
Ego autem in eris quasi habens esse
freezing I've been here for two weeks
Ego hic est glacians duas hebdomades
it's like it's like that time I got a
Et sicut tempus est ut suus 'got a se
root canal and for one whole hour I
Radix et fossa unius hora
couldn't say a thing and everything I
non enim est dicere quod non omne
thought was hilarious and I'm like oh
O me sicut cogitatio et hilares
yes yeah like oh playback yeah all the
O Yeah playback memini etiam ut omnes
best things are when you can't talk we
quae sunt maxime cum hoc non possunt loqui
tonight are going to be looking at fake
noctem respiciens ad ire ut fake
SD cards I talked about it a couple of
SD pecto super illud loquebatur in me duobus
weeks back and tonight one might be on
et in hac occidetur quisquam
its way to us whoa stick around
Heus suos viam nobis ad inhaero circum
[Music]
[Musica]
for a limited time get your hands on
stricto super tempore ad adepto manus vestras
limited-edition shirts from the category
-Shirt Genus limitata editions
5 TV network these high quality shirts
V TV network qualis haec altus-shirts
are manufactured by teespring
fabricari per teespring
a fundraising website and your purchase
a fundraising vestri website et emptio
will help support the shows we produce
support ostendit nobis ad producendum auxiliatus sum
get yours today and send us your
tibi hodie, ut nos tui et mitte
pictures to be featured on the
ut featured in imaginibus
corresponding show visit cap 5 dot TV
respondens V cap dat TV ostende visita
slash shirts to support us and get your
exacuere vade ad sindones, nos adepto vestri
official Network shirt today cap five
Network publica quinque shirt hodie c
dot TV slash shirts welcome back this is
shirts dat TV VULNUS receperint reversus est
category five technology TV now a few
Lorem numerus quinque TV pauca
weeks ago we talked about fake SD cards
SD pecto de fake nos loquebatur weeks ago
being available on Amazon and and what I
praesto esse et quid est quod me Amazon
want to it kind of answer the question
genus vis ad quod respondendum quaestio
because the questions have been coming
quia interrogationes sunt veniens
in in full force mm-hmm people on
hmm in suo robore permansuris mm-populo
YouTube people sending us email and
Et nos misso email Juvenis populi
commenting on our website saying um
um dicere Commentator in nostro
would Amazon really sell a fake SD card
SD card vere vendere Amazon non est fake
so what I want to know is could a fake
Quid me vis nosse non poterant est fake
SD card actually be real
SD card actu reali
oh and by real I mean could it actually
O possit actu vult et verus essem
be fake yes could it be so let's say I'm
et ego lets 'narro ut fake esse non posse sic;
just gonna switch over to my computer
sicut agnus dei switch super ad computatrum
here and let's jump over to Amazon CA my
lets 'hic, et salire ad CA Amazon meum
shopping portal and let's do a quick
et in facio velox shopping portal
search here I'm gonna do a 256 gigabyte
hic me quaerere in CCLVI gigabyte laudibus?
micro SD and I can see
Micro SD, et non videbunt
oh yeah the cost is well over a hundred
O Yeah est pretium centum
bucks for these kind of things so
Haec et talia leones
remember we're gonna be using this in
memores sumus ut usura is in amet
our video camera so we want to shoot a
video camera nostra tam Nos volo ut sagittent in
wedding with this now this one's cheaper
hoc nunc est scriptor nuptialem hanc cheaper
but it's only 128 gigs again 256 gigs
sed solum illud iterum CXXVIII gigs CCLVI gigs
Samsung it's a bit heavy so let's sort
Samsung suus 'aliquantulus gravibus ita lets genus
by price because that's what I do on
quod illud est quod facis de pretio a te
Amazon right and whoa Sasha can you
Heus Not Amazon fas et vos
believe it 256 gigs for like under 10
sicut credimus factum in X de CCLVI gigs
bucks you ate it to steal it sounds like
et illos leones, quos comedit eam non sonat furantur
it this looks totally legit 256
Hoc spectat CCLVI prorsus legit illud
gigabytes its class 10 obviously it
X autem manifesto gigantocteti genus suum
looks the best chip and flash mob
volgus videt optimos DOLO ictu
Jules and it's only ten bucks
Quod suus 'tantum decem illos leones, quos C.
Oh okay I've got to take a look at the
O bene ut ad vultus ad Ego got
reviews because I got to be smart about
quia dolor sit de obtinuit recensiones
this now there's only two and a half out
Nunc hoc tantum in dupondium semissem
of five stars this guy I mean it seems
huic ego videtur sidera quinque
like oh yeah they definitely are happy
O felix yeah ut pro certo
with this purchase okay yeah uh-huh
yeah bene uh-emptio hoc huh
oh there's a lot of one-star reviews now
O illic 'multus-stella reviews modo unius
when I see these one-star reviews and I
et cum haec una stella reviews
start kind of skimming these I start to
Iamque tincidunt haec initium quoddam
think sash of it you know what they
quid tibi videtur serica
probably they just they got a lemon yeah
probabiliter quod non solum got a yeah lemon
they got a lemon I mean there's a
they got a CITREA sit non a me
there's 400 reviews Plus here so I'm
illic 'et hie me plus recensiones CD
gonna add this to cart because you know
agnus dei addere hoc scis quia cart
what it's worth the risk of $10
id enim periculum suus 'dignitas of $ X
I can definitely spend $10 I mean look
Certus sum sit intueri possum habe $ X
at the price of a normal 256 gig SD card
ad normalis pretium est GIg SD card CCLVI
so this is definitely a steal I regret
et furantur hoc est certus a me pœnitet
that those folks got a lemon but I think
sed puto ea esse folks got a CITREA
you know I'm gonna play I'm gonna take
Im 'agnus dei agnus dei ludere nosti me sume
the risk yeah and let's that let's give
Yeah melius est esse periculo dandum sit
it a go place the order
ut illam ire constituit
free shipping yeah prime all right who
liber primus yeah shipping omnium qui recte
could that be oh okay um just one second
Secundo purus quis poterit vnus um
here sorry to do this to you folks huh
non hic tibi triste sem huh
Amazon's gotten really fast these days
Amazon suus 'vere nactus celeriter hos dies
all right well let's bring this over
super hoc omnium optime scriptor
here to our unboxing table and let's get
hinc ad mensam et lets 'adepto unboxing
a look here this got to be a fake at $10
hinc est quod surrexit ad $ X esse fake
but let's get into the package bit would
in sarcina frenum volunt accipere, sed lets
wait a minute this actually came from
quod etiam factum ab manere unus minutam
Amazon this is the Mississauga Amazon
Mississauga est hoc Amazon Amazon
warehouse so this didn't come from some
non ita ex horreis
obscure Chinese factory or something
seu quod Chinese factory obscuris
like that no this came directly from
ut hoc non directe
amazon.ca explaining why it was so fast
amazon.ca explicare cur retinebantur
exactly all right oh yeah look at that
prorsus omne ius yeah o aspice
oh it is a micro SDHC memory card new
Quis est novum memoria card Flash
made in China it's a memory card as we
in Sinis dum illud memoriam card
learned on the front plug-and-play for
didici a fronte ut ludere plug-and-
digital cameras cellular phones oh it
digital cameras cellular phones quod utinam
even does PDA is just in case you still
si quidem iustum est Adhuc enim PDA
use a PDA like high-speed
uti sicut summus celeritas a PDA
high-performance this sounds incredible
summus altum perficientur hoc incredibile iudicatur
for only 10 bucks I'll get into it all
solum X youll 'adepto illos leones, quos ego in illo omnes
right let's take a look here this can't
hic scriptor vultu non rectum
be real I mean they've got a sticker
ego teneo ut verum non sit a sticker
over it it's got to be a fake no that
in hoc quod non est fake, ut suus 'got esse
looks completely legit to me all right
videtur omnino recte legit mihi
it's
suus '
see if I can just get in there okay yeah
in tantum ut non videatur, si non bene yeah
yeah there we go all right let's get a
yeah lets adepto a dextris est enim omnis
look at this so there's a micro SD card
Micro videre nihil tam SD card
right there is it a five gig at that
non est autem ius quinque gig
price it's got to be like 16 gigs now no
pretium suus 'got ut iam non sit similis XVI gigs
that's actually a 256 gigabyte micro SD
quod quidem CCLVI gigabyte Micro SD
card for the win I'm shocked this is
card ad hoc win Sum abhorrent
legit Sasha so let's throw this in the
Not sic lets haec legit mittent ad
camera all right all right so we've got
Comperto totum jus et fas omne camera
it in our camera we're ready to start
nos sumus parati in diam tincidunt
shooting video at my cousin's wedding
video surculus donis patruelibus orbi ad nuptias
right right
dextera dextrae
it formats the camera reads it the
in camera illa in formats legit illud
camera shows that it's 256 gigs for yep
ostendit, quod suus 'gigs enim yep camera CCLVI
that's a win it's good
quia bonum factum est a win
it's obviously legit 256 gig card for
CCLVI card legit in manifesto illud cisiis pervolavit
only $9.99 right steel score and do you
tantum $ 9.99 jus score ferro, et vos facite
see any doubt in my eyes any doubt in my
dubium dubium cuiquam oculis meis
eyes whatsoever I have Linux installed
Linux oculos quaecumque elit
on my computer folks Linux gives me
Linux meo computatrum folks dederit mihi
power beyond measure and I can figure
ultra modum, et instar potentia potest,
things out that maybe you can't do on a
fortasse non est in rebus
normal system in quite as little time
Duis ratio paulo minus
tonight we're gonna look at this micro
hac nocte vultus sumus agnus dei in hac micro
SD card that Amazon shipped me let's get
SD card, qui me amet lets 'adepto Amazon
a little bit of a close-up look here a
ad finem usque pauco heus
256 gigabyte micro SD card we're gonna
CCLVI gigabyte Micro SD card, sumus agnus dei
take a look at that in Linux and find
Linux take a vultus in tempore illo, et invenies
out is this for real
hoc verum esse ex
okay let's back up a few weeks right we
Accumsan cor eius et pauca jure
have to talk about the folks who
de folks qui habent loqui
actually did this and bought this off of
et emit et is off fecit hoc
Amazon plugged it into their DSLR and it
DSLR inplenda est et in Amazon
was working fantastically well right so
et fantastically bene rectum opus
they shot a wedding with it
quod exortum est in ea nuptias
they did and they shot the whole thing
et dedit illi totum
and then they got at home and they went
et surrexerunt abieruntque domi
to edit the video and everything on the
ut video emendo et super omnia
card was corrupt why would that happen
Corrupta card cur fieret
well because a fake micro SD card will
bene est quia fake autem micro SD card
in fact only be say let's say it's a 16
In eo modo dicat quod lets 'dicere a XVI
gig micro SD that they hacked the
Micro SD ferientum ut gig
firmware of to trick your camera into
ad avaritiam ex firmware in camera
thinking it's 256 gigs and then they
tunc illud existimans CCLVI services
reprinted the silk-screening to make it
Editio-protegendo sericum est ad eam
look like physically
tamquam realiter
it's 256 gigs so yeah but when you plug
suus 'gigs CCLVI yeah, ut non cum obturaculum
it in because they've hacked the the
propter detruncati in et ex theyve '
firmware the the bootloader the boot
in tabernus de de firmware bootloader
sectors in whatever else of the drive
aliud coegi sectoribus
your camera your device your phone
camera tuum phone fabrica
thinks it's 256 gigs so then it hits
Ergo videtur services CCLVI percusserit eam
that 16 gig cap because it's
XVI cap quia cisiis pervolavit quod suus '
legitimately not 256 gigs it's only say
CCLVI suus 'gigs legitime, non dico tantum,
16 gigs and when it hits that cap it
Et cum haberi non capitulo XVI services
still keeps recording and starts and it
memoria et servat ea, et usque animi
thinks that it's 256 gigs so there's
suus 'non ut illic' gigs cogitat, CCLVI
lots of space
lots of locus
but where's it putting that data the
data est ut sit ubi est ponere
chips that are within this card if this
quod si intra eu card
is indeed fake but in the instance of a
immo est fake, sed ab instantia
fake card is not going to be able to
Ad possit card est non fake
write the data it's gonna look like it's
suus 'agnus dei notitia vultus amo scribe super illud
there because it's recording the file
memoria est quod suus 'a lima
names and everything else but it may not
nisi ut aliud non esse, et omne nomen
be there so how do we actually tell well
unde etiam bene dicere non est ita
we have unboxed this now tonight we've
Weve 'iam hac nocte nos unboxed
got a SD card micro SD card reader I'm
Micro SD card legit Im 'got a SD card
just gonna simply plug that in I'll set
Et posuit sicut agnus dei tantum ut plug
this aside because there's a USB 3
quia non est seorsum a USB III
memory card reader and let's bring up
Reader melius memoriam revocare
our Linux laptop here and I'm just going
Im 'iens sicut laptop Linux nos huc
to jump into the terminal now I'm gonna
ut salire in in terminatio nunc ego Im 'agnus dei
say just straight off oh and let's let's
sicut et statim dicunt lets 'O lets'
see what I can do here about the display
quid hic rebus possum
because you're not seeing what I see
quia 'non quid sum cum viderem
well let's quickly can I bring this can
huius bring non potest bene fieri cito Sit scriptor
I just drag that over to it yeah that
Qui convertit ut memini duco
works alright folks let's see if I can
licet videamus si possumus opera folks
just kind of no it won't let me zoom in
iustum est nulla erit in me zoom
so I hope that you're using a high
ut per spem quae erant in excelsis
enough resolution that you can see that
vides consultum satis
very very well but I'm gonna walk you
sed ipsum tam Im 'agnus dei vestri deambulatio
through there we go I'm gonna walk you
Per me itur Im 'agnus dei esse ambulate
through everything that I'm gonna do
Omnia autem facio propter Im 'agnus dei
here so first of all I'm doing this on
ut primum hoc facio hic
Linux you can figure this out on
Linux vos can instar sicco super hoc
Microsoft Windows stick around if you're
Si vestri 'inhaero circa Fenestra Microsoft
on Microsoft Windows I'm going to tell
Im 'iens ut dicam in Fenestra Microsoft
you how you can do this on Windows if
quomodo possum, si tibi hoc in Fenestra
you do not have Linux but Linux is free
Linux non est nisi quod liberum Linux
you can install it and then you can do
Potest autem et vos install potestis facere
this and it's much much quicker now I
et quod suus 'quanto celerior tantum nunc
don't have a fear Sasha that Mac users
non metus sasha Mac users
ever have this problem because a Mac
hoc problema semper quoniam a Mac
user is gonna go to Amazon and they're
et tu user Amazon sit amet ire
gonna see the cheap card and they're
et tu videbis card agnus dei cheap
gonna skip right over them to the really
et super ea re in ius amet skip
expensive cards right and then they're
et qui pretiosa cards ius es
gonna multiply the price of the really
et multiplicamini amet pretium realiter
expensive card by three and that's the
card pretiosa sunt per tribus et ut '
one that they're gonna buy great they're
quod aliquis se magnis amet emere es
buying the $300 256 gigs right
buying a dextris gigs $ CCC CCLVI
they're just expecting that in two years
exspectat ut erant 'non iustus duo annis,
they'll have to buy another one anyway
non enim te emere nemo usquam alius
exactly so Mac users this is not for you
Hoc est enim tam exacte Mac users
I understand that you've never tried to
Intelligo tu umquam conatus est
find something at this price point but
in hoc quod iam non invenient pretium
for you Windows and Linux users who are
Linux quod Fenestra users tibi qui sunt,
looking for a deal you might fall for
paciscor vos vultus parumper cadunt
this if you go onto Amazon so what we're
Haec si vos onto Amazon Quid sumus
gonna do on our Linux machine first of
Linux a nobis primo machina laudibus?
all I'm going to become super user so
Im 'iens ut facti Super omnibus ergo usor
sudo su on my this is Linux Mint aka
sudo an mei haec New aka Linux
this one's based on Ubuntu so sudo su
Unus fundatur Ubuntu est hoc, ut su sudo
for any of those or just su su on a
sive per aliquem eorum in mox Su Su
Debian system and I'm going to install a
Debian quod ratio ad install Im 'iens
program called f3 so apt install f3 it's
f3 dicitur aptas progressio install f3 suus '
gonna quickly grab that from the
Abbas capto propere ab
repositories there we go and let's run
et venimus repositoria est scriptor run
the program so we're gonna run f3 probe
progressio sic amet averso specillo diducendum currere f3
and here's where I actually well I can't
tum ubi actum est quod hic non possum
really proceed because I haven't plugged
quod non procedat vere SUPERGESTUS
in my microSD card yet so let's do that
microSD tamen ut in card quod faciamus
first first of all I need to know what
primum debeo quid primum omnium
drive this is going to be I'm going to
Im 'iens ut eiciam quo vado
ctrl C so I'm going to go LS space now
Eo accidit, ut C ad spatium iam LS
remember I am super user so I can do
Super user recordabor ego facio et non possum
this dev slash
hoc Dev VULNUS
SD star enter and IC SD a SD a 1 SD a 2
Stella enim a SD SD SD intraveritis, IC ad II I SD
so the built-in computer hard drive on
ita constructum-in die computatrum difficile agitare
my computer is SDA ok so now what I'm
ok SDA meus computer est iam et quid ego sum,
gonna do is I'm gonna connect my USB
Non est agnus Im 'agnus dei mei coniungere USB
reader right ok and as soon as I do that
Lector jure facere ut OK
now Linux is going to probably detect a
Nunc Linux probabiliter quod facturus sit deprehendere
couple of new drives quite possibly
duobus novis forsitan agit
let's see maybe not but what I can do is
videamus non datur inpiis, sed quid facere possum
now I can run that same command LS / o
iam can run idem mandatum LS / O
it is detecting something that seemed to
est facilius deprehendamus videbantur esse aliquid
kind of jump around there a little bit o
Salire circa genus o paulo
on my other screen it is it's brought up
aliud tentorium meum et eduxit eam
a drive here which I can close and over
hic et claudere possum Coegi
here I'm gonna run that same command
hic run idem Im 'agnus dei mandatum
what I'm telling it to do is show me all
Im 'sit facere ut vera quae mihi omnia,
the devices that start with SD cuz that
quod cogitationes quae committitur cuz SD
asterisk SD being like a hard drive if
SD Si asterisco instar ferreus coegi
you don't know which my USB Drive is
USB Coegi meum, et nescio, quae sit
being detected as and you can see that
et non videre potest quod correptus
now I've got SD b and SD b1 so let's now
Ego got D Nunc lets nunc ergo b et D b1
remember I installed f3 but before I do
et meminisse me prius facio installed f3
that I'm going to go F disk
Im 'iens ut orbis, ut F
- L /dev / s DB now that we've
- L / dev / DB modo quod Ive 's
determined that that is my drive and lo
quia non est constituta atque lo coegi
and behold its 245 gigabytes
et ecce CCXLV gigantocteti
yes yeah there you go there you go
yeah tu enim est quod sic te
that's what your computer shows you
quae tibi ostendit quod computatrum tuum
that's what windows will show you that's
id quod fenestras ostendam vobis ut '
what Mac will show you that's what your
quod Mac ostendam tibi quid te ut '
camera will show you that's what your
hoc camera ostendam vobis quid tibi est
phone will show you so how do we
phone ostendam tibi quid nobis et quomodo
determine whether or not this is legit
utrum sit necne legis
is it really a 256 gig or what is being
est vere ens est id quod est, vel CCLVI cisiis pervolavit
reported as 245 gig SD card so that's
CCXLV cisiis pervolavit relatum ut ut SD card, ut '
where f3 comes in so let's do f3 probe
in f3 venit in f3 ut quid averso specillo repellendum lets '
now that we know that it is dev slash SD
SD quod nunc scimus quod Dev VULNUS
b i'm gonna go - - this is a brand new
Im 'agnus dei b ire - - hoc novam
card so we're gonna do a destructive
card ita et nos in laudibus? perniciosius
test Oh which we want to do anyways
test quam vis ut faciam tibi, o anyways
because it's the most accurate for this
quia hoc verissimum est
really really quick test but it will
re vera velox realiter test illud autem erit
destroy some data if you have data on
si notitia notitia aliquam
there so don't do this on a car that
hoc enim non est super currus illius
you've already used a destructive test
uti te iam a test perniciosius
just like it is gonna overwrite sectors
est sicut agnus dei industrias rescribere
of the drive and that's going to read
suus 'iens per coegi et legere
those sectors back to say hey did that
aer discrimina accipit tergum ut diceret illi heu quae fecit
actually work or did it lie to me and
etiam operemur, non mentiri me, et non fecit
say that it would work but it didn't
quod autem factum esset opus non
okay right are we gonna get corrupted
bene nobis 'agnus dei adepto dextris sunt corrupta
data so the reason we're using f3 as
et data ex causa quia erant 'usura f3
opposed to some of the tools that are
qui in aliquo opponitur instrumenta
out there is because f3 probe can do
f3 averso specillo repellendum est, quia sicco illic potestis facere
this extremely quickly so where it may
maxime ubi est tam celeriter ut
take 6 hours on a 256 gigabyte Drive
VI horas accipere in CCLVI gigabyte Coegi
using traditional means and on Microsoft
Microsoft est usura traditional media et
Windows here on Linux with f3 probe it's
Linux in Fenestra hic explorare suus in f3
gonna take under 15 minutes perfect ok
ok sumo perfectus in XV minuta amet
and sometimes just seconds just seconds
et seconds interdum justo justo seconds
so - - destructive - - the type of tests
tam - - perniciosius - - species per probat
we're gonna do time ops slash dev slash
exacuere vade Opis tempus erant 'Dev VULNUS laudibus?
and what was the drive Sascha I'm just
et quid est Sascha coegi Non sum,
quizzing you SDP SDB sorry member that's
SDB, qui socius suus SDP contristati estis quaerere
important because if I accidentally
Si accidens, quia magni momenti
typed SDA that's my hard drive in my
qui SDA mihi typed dura coegi meo
laptop right I'm gonna overwrite sectors
Im 'agnus dei industrias ius laptop overwrite
on my actual hard drive don't make that
Non quia dura coegi ipsam meis
mistake be very very careful of this
hoc ipsum magnopere errasse
command I'm going to hit enter and it
Im 'iens ut intraret, et imperium ledo
says warning probing normally takes a
testimonium enim accipit scrutantium recipiunt, inquit Northmanni
few seconds
brevi tempore
- 15 minutes but it can take longer
- XV minuta, sed non potest, ut iam
please be patient
placere patientes estote
so what this is doing right now Sasha
Quid agis hic nunc Not
yes it is
sic est,
writing random points on this drive so
ita scribo temere puncta hac coegi
it knows that it's supposed to be 256
Scit suus 'supponitur, est quod CCLVI
gigabytes right and so it'll write
Itaque iam bene scribendi gigabytes
something at 10 gigabytes and it'll
quod ad X gigantocteti, et si tibi placet
write something at 4 gigabytes and it'll
IV scribere aliquid ad gigantocteti et si tibi placet
write something at 20 gigabytes and
scribere aliquid ad quod XX gigantocteti
something at 100 gigabytes and something
quod in C quodque gigantocteti
up 500 gigabytes and it'll read it back
et in D gigantocteti eam youll legere
and it'll say does this match what I
ego dicam tibi quod et factum est hoc par
wrote and if at any point it sees that
et scripsit ut si qua parte non videt
it's not actually matching then it's
tunc suus 'matching in actu, suus'
gonna figure out ok well where does this
ubi 'agnus dei hoc bene ok instar sicco
Drive actually end off and we're gonna
Eiciam actually terminus off et amet
find out how big the drive actually is
ex quo magnum se habet ad coegi inveniet
but what makes me nervous smashes is
sed quid est Smashes nervosi me
there a chance that the $10.00 SD card
est facultas quod SD card $ 10.00
could be legit I feel like there's like
legit sentio amo non erunt ut illic '
a 0-0 percent chance there's pretty much
0-0 percent forte est ibi pulchra valde
a zero point zero percent chance oh it's
nullus punctus sit percent forte nullus suus 'O
done oh ok what do we got
Quis autem quid fecit urna
ladies and gentlemen bad news see that
ut videas malum dominarum et iudices nuntium
if I got bad news this device dev slash
si haec mala fabrica surrexit Dev VULNUS
SDB is a counterfeit of type limbo ha
SDB archiep sit adulterinum ipsius limbi generis ha
the actual device geometry and it only
nisi ea re Geometricis &amp; fabrica
took a couple of moments here the usable
adsumptis duobus temporibus hic utilis
size of this drive ladies and gentlemen
mole huius dominarum et iudices coegi
is 15 point six six gigabytes the
XV in hoc loco sex gigantocteti sex
announced size is 245 gigabytes
nuntiatum est CCXLV mole gigantocteti
Hauser's ladies and gentlemen we have
Hauser de dominarum et iudices nos habere
purchased a fake micro SD card from
Micro SD card possedit fictus
Amazon legitimately yeah Amazon dot CA
Yeah Amazon Amazon legitime CA dot
shipped directly from their warehouse
CELLA amet directe ab
right yes they're going to be hearing
Ecce auditum iri recte agant
from me yes I'm going to be returning
et reversus est de me, sic Im 'iens
the card yes I am furious because I shot
card sic in furore quia ego confodietur
that whole wedding and I'm going to sue
nuptialem omnis et quia vado ad petendam
now here's the let's back up again I
Iterum iam hic in tergo ultimi
love doing this think about the scenario
amat cogitare id sem
right at the beginning of this Sasha we
Principio nobis ius Not
decided we determined it's worth the
suus 'dignitas ad determinari diximus placuit
risk of 10 dollars because my 10 dollars
X X pupa pupa, quod de periculo meo
that's like five cups of coffee right
quod, sicut capulus quinque pocula dextra
right it's worth that risk I might save
jus illud periculum tanti facerem salvos
ninety five dollars or a hundred
trecenti nonaginta quinque aut pupa
right what is the value that you would
quod ius pretii quod vellet
put on say your wedding video it's I'm
Dicunt suus 'ego video te nuptias induendum
raising that example because this is
suscitans quia gratia
like it's like like worth what would I
sicut dignum est ut tibi placet quod vellet
spend to get it back if I didn't have it
quod si eam non habere ut expendas
a lot of money how would I feel and this
quomodo sentio et opibus
is rhetorical for everyone and and using
Rhetorica est, et quia omnis usus, et
wedding video maybe that's not the
nuptialem video, non est qui maybe
example that is applicable to you but
exemplum autem hoc observandum erit in vobis:
something that is priceless to you
quid est quod pulcherrimum est ad te,
photos on your phone contacts files that
in phone contactus files qui photos
are important to you what if you hit
Quid ad te magni momenti sunt si vos ledo
that 16 gig limit of the physical disk
XVI Quod finis cisiis pervolavit orbem in physical
mm-hmm and kept saving to it and lost
perierat, et salvis atque hmm mm
everything else that you saved what was
Cur reliquis quae
that worth the $10 was that worth saving
ut dignum esset ut dignum est $ X salvis
not a potentially saving $90 and it is a
salvis $ XC est, et non in potentia,
rhetorical question the answer is
rhetoricae quaestio responsum est,
absolutely not now this is a fake micro
Hoc est omnino non modo fake Micro
SD card and this tool f3 and in this
SD card et f3 et instrumentum hoc
particular instance of this example f3
huius exemplum causae statim f3
probe the application that comes with it
hoc fit per applicationem ad ea quae facimus exploramus alterius
is showing us on Linux that the drive is
ostendens quemadmodum et is in coegi ut est Linux
actually only a 16 gig drive now whoever
XVI cisiis pervolavit iam coegi vere non est qui
hacked it whoever sold this illegal fake
qui venundatus est hoc iniustum caederetur ruebat fake
drive on Amazon or to Amazon and put it
Amazon Amazon dedit agitare uel
in their warehouse hacked the firmware
in CELLA firmware caedere tegmina
hacked the chip to make it think and
ut cogitare laceratus chip
make a trickier device into thinking
atque consilio existimaret trickier
that it is 256 gigs or reporting as 245
quod vel CCLVI services ut reporting CCXLV
gigs but in fact it is not now the drive
sed hoc non iam coegi gigs
may be usable and so f3 fix is included
f3 fix sit utilis et est includi
and has given you the command to be able
et dedi tibi imperium esse poterit
to use the full 16 gig space so I could
XVI cisiis pervolavit ad plenam spatium ut poterant
convert this into a 16 gig card and
Hoc card et convertet in XVI cisiis pervolavit
start using it but that's not what I
sed ut satus usura ut 'non sum
bought and if I had recorded to it I
et emit me memoriae est, si sum eam
would have lost practically everything
amissa esse fere omnia
that I had written to it because how
quid est quod scripsisti ad me
quickly do you fill 16 gigs with a 4k
XVI imples cum citius 4k services
camera or your DSLR it just boom
Canon enim tuus sicut camera, vel boom
lickety-split just like that
ut, sicut split Lickety
so stay away from those fake drives if
discedite agit nisi ut ab his fake
you see those red flags what do we look
qui vides quid possumus quaerere ruber flaccescit
for well too good to be true prices
Bene enim pretium quod bonum et verum,
absolutely bad reviews bad reviews are
absolute malum reviews malos sed recensiones
definitely something now they're not
certus quod doluere non
always the case because bad reviews
quia malum semper recenseo
maybe you do have to I kind of joke
quaedam ioco fortasse non habent
about it and alluded to it you sometimes
numquam te et circa eam innuit,
have to say oh that person obviously
dic mihi, o homo, qui manifesto
doesn't know what they're talking about
Nescio quid erant 'non loquitur de
a fresh new company very brand a company
nova turba autem nova turba nota nimis
that just started up right and really
Iustus coepi, quod iustum est et realiter
you know you you can't really find out
re vobis scio vos non potes reperire ex
about them yes definitely definitely I
sic EGO certus certus de illa
can't think of anything else those are
Sunt equidem aliud
really good red flags yeah bad reviews
yeah vere bonum malum reviews ruber flaccescit
and perpetually bad reviews right and
perpetuoque jure malum reviews
look at look at the good reviews - okay
at per bonum recensiones vultus - bene
can I say that can I suggest that one
possum dicere possum, quod nemo suadeant
way to tell if it's a fake product is to
ut dico si suus 'a uber est fake
look at the good reviews because if the
at si bonae recenseo quod
good reviews are so glowing and so poor
sed recensiones quoque tam rutilans, ut bonus et pauper
in their English a lot of times I hate
multum in Anglis temporibus odi
to say it but a lot of times that they
nisi quod semper multum loquaris
are possibly hired by the company who's
fortassis quis dolor conducta
doing this fraud or perhaps the same
Forte hoc idem fraude
people and they're adding this to that
et eos, qui ad hoc erant addendo
to offset all those bad reviews and it
et omnes male etiamnunc recenseo
does happen this is legit right well you
Contingit autem hoc probe capiat
can also be frozen out of being able to
congelari potest etiam esse potest ab
write a review which is an
quae est write a review
after-the-fact problem right so you're
et hoc problema ius post-the-es
like oh this is this is a bad device and
Quis similis est et haec ratio mali
then you go to write a review and you're
igitur tu es et tu in write a review
frozen out of it you can't it's quite
congelatus est Non potes satis ex eo
sure I can post this video yes and and I
certe ego video fieri post haec, et quod sic et
hope that I save you from accidentally
Spero salvare forte
believing that a ten dollar 256 gigabyte
in credendo ut decem pupa CCLVI gigabyte
microSD card exists now if you're on
card nunc microSD existit nisi in te
Microsoft Windows we've got a link for
Comperto Fenestra Microsoft ad nexum
you a cat5 dot TV / USB test and that
CAT5 dat vobis TV / USB atque test
will take you to this blog entry at
tollet vos ad hoc video
Raymond dot CC that has been sent to us
Cc, qui dat nobis missum Raymond
courtesy of David fear a viewer who was
Affabilitatem David videntium qui erat, et timeo
watching and commented on our YouTube
commentatione nobis vigilantes YouTube
channel so thank you David for sending
gratias ago tibi, quia ut mittam channel David
this in now this blog entry number one
Hoc video in numero
shows us to use H to test W which is a
quo probare H. W ostendit nobis uti est,
very well-respected tool to do this very
honos, ut bene hoc instrumentum
test on Microsoft Windows so if you're
Microsoft Fenestra test, ut si vestri '
not on Linux you can use this tool and
non poteris uti Linux et instrumentum hoc
it's going to take a lot longer than a
suus 'iens accipere multum ultra
Linux tool that we showed you tonight
Ut ostendit Linux instrumentum hac nocte
but it's going to do the job for you and
tamen suus 'non iens ut pro te et officium
show you whether that USB flash drive or
USB mico coegi ut tibi aut si
in this case a micro SD
hac de causa micro SD
card is in fact legit or if it's fake
card legit in hoc vel illud fake
stick around we've got more show for you
circa inhaero plus Comperto ostende te
coming up whether you shop on thinkgeek
TABERNA num usque venire te in ThinkGeek
gearbest B&amp;H photo video eBay or Amazon
video Amazon eBay vel photo gearbest B &amp; B
or even if you want a free trial of
Si voles de libera aut etiam iudicii
audible you'll find the best deals and
et exeunti youll 'reperio optima agit
support the shows we produce by simply
support producendum per quod simpliciter ostendit nobis
visiting the shopping sites you already
iam situs visitare shopping
frequent by using the links on our
ad frequentes utendo nexus nobis
website visit category 5 TV slash
genus website visita TV VULNUS V
partners for the full and ever-growing
sociis ad plenum cotidie
list and help us create more free
auxilium creare plus mittat et libera nos,
content like this show thank you for
sic Wisi enim ad spectaculum contentus
shopping with our partners and thank you
et sociis nostris mercatum it cum gratias ago tibi,
for watching welcome back this is
et spectant retro receperint est
category 5 technology TV now Sasha over
Not in V genus technology TV nunc
the past couple of weeks I've been
Ego aliquot hebdomades praeterita fuerint
looking for a Linux distribution to help
vultus parumper Linux distribution auxiliari
me migrate my laptop over to Linux right
Linux meus laptop profugus ad dextram meam
I need to be able to do video editing
Potest facere opus esse video edendis
though that's like crucial to me with my
quamquam id cum mea mecum est quasi magnae
Linux yeah but you also still want to do
Linux yeah sed etiam vis ut faciam tibi
yes and so now we looked at LMDE
nunc itaque sic intuens LMDE
yes and I love it I'm actually quite
ita non amor et re vera ego sum satis
impressed with it it's Debian based but
sed secundum debian quod suus cum impressa
I couldn't quite get my video editor to
Ego non adepto satis esse mihi video Editor
work on it so then I thought okay maybe
Bene itaque fortasse putarem opus
I could try Linux Mint the actual Linux
Linux experiri potui Linux ipsam New
Mint 19 because it's based on a boon -
XIX, quod suus fundatur in boon New -
and I know that it probably has more
et nescit quod est magis verisimile
current proprietary drivers for Nvidia
NVIDIA est proprietary current coegi
and those kinds of things are a lot
et species multum
easier to take care of on Linux Mint
facile ad curam Acceptable in Linux
than they are on LMDE 3 freights
sunt onera magis quam super LMDE III
for examples so I was able to get Linux
et quia exempla non poterat adepto Linux
Mint installed and I got DaVinci Resolve
Installed mentham, et obtinuit DaVinci velis
installed but I was horribly
nisi tempestate perculsi mutaverunt installed fui
disappointed in not Linux Mint not Linux
Nonne Mint Linux Linux non frustra
but in DaVinci Resolve that it says
Dicit enim quod volo sed DaVinci
your hardware is not good enough for
non satis hardware pro vestra
this stuff Robbie oh and I said who
haec et dixi heu quis supellectilem Robbie
cares about my screen resolution I get
ut curat de me screen resolutio
in there and I start doing video editing
et video edendis esse in satus faciens
and it says you're at a memory your your
inquit, et tuorum tibi ad memoriam tui
GPU can't keep up and all this kind of
Omnia possum in hac GPU
stuff and then I start thinking I do
materia satus ratus deinde ego
video editing on here on Microsoft
Microsoft edere de video quae habetur in via
Windows 10 all the time
X Fenestra omni tempore,
mm-hmm CyberLink PowerDirector 14 is
hmm hoc XIV-mm Cyberlink PowerDirector
what I'm currently using I'll probably
Im 'usura id quod sum currently youll verisimile
upgrade because we do sometimes do some
Phasellus interdum facere aliquid quod non
360 stuff but it works flawlessly mm-hmm
Sed illud operatur flawlessly supellectilem CCCLX-mm hmm
so why can't DaVinci Resolve handle
quare non solvit DaVinci tractare
editing on my same computer and so it's
edere computatrum mei simul et suus '
not a Linux vs. Windows thing it's a
vs. Fenestra Linux non est eam vir suus '
CyberLink PowerDirector versus DaVinci
Cyberlink PowerDirector versus DaVinci
Resolve thing and I really love the idea
Ego vere diligit, et res propono in ideam
of DaVinci Resolve but it seems to me
sed puto et volo DaVinci
like I'd have to upgrade and upgrade an
sicut ego tibi an upgrade Phasellus
upgrade buy a better laptop it's getting
Phasellus buy a laptop suus questus melius
aged I have man we've had this one for
Non habeo virum senem ad weve habebat unus est
many years here at the studio but it
multis annis ad studio hic autem eo
still does the job on Windows for
tamen officium agit in Fenestra
editing with CyberLink mm-hmm
recensere cum Cyberlink mm, hmm
so do you take that approach of
et accipe tibi accessus
investing money into the thing and
et pecuniam in hoc
buying new one and now why don't I just
cur ego novi et ementes
buy a Mac if I have that mine right but
et si dextera mea, quae in me emere Mac
and that's the second time in this show
et in hoc secundo ostendo ut '
that we've dissed Mac and that's what
et dissed postquam ei reí Hoc illud est quod Mac
this shows about folks so if you're here
si tu haec ita hic ostendit super folks
for the first time I don't want to take
primum non vis accipere
that approach because it already works I
et quia iam prope est opus
don't like to replace things that I
quae mihi non placet reponere
already have right I'm not that mindset
Im 'non prius quod habere ius questae
right you want to be able to use what
ius vis esse potest ad id quod
you have but for the purpose that suits
ad quod habetis sed decet
you best right right and I dream of
maxime recta et non recta somnium
being able to go 100% exclusive Linux
Linux exclusive ens possint ad C%
doing all my video editing and doing
facientem omnia et faciens video edendis
everything else everything else I only
quae non aliud aliud nisi omne
do on Linux web surf and email
et in salo Linux tela et inscriptio
everything else I do documents
Omnia agam aliud documentis
everything is Linux programming
Linux programming enim omnia
especially I hate doing it on Windows it
Odio faciens eam maxime quod Fenestra
sucks but on Linux is fantastic so I
in Linux non est fantastic sic sugit
have to take the approach and say okay
ut in aduentu et bene dicunt,
what what else can I do what can I do
quibus agam, quod aliud quid facitis
here and then I thought Sasha what if
et si ego hic Not
what if I took away that dependency and
quod si et dependentia Abstulit
said okay it's telling me my laptop
dicitur mihi dicere suus 'okay laptop
ain't good enough yeah I know it's good
ego scio suus 'non satis bona yeah
enough
satis
right it ain't good enough to run
ius est non satis currere
DaVinci Resolve 15 but I know it's good
XV volo DaVinci scio suus 'non bonam
enough for CyberLink PowerDirector 14
Sufficit enim Cyberlink XIV PowerDirector
right I'm happy with it
Im 'laetus quod iustum est
it's fantastic so what if I do a boot it
si quod suus 'fantastic sic ego non vir eius tabernus
what if I take the approach of saying
quod si accipere et ait approach
let's just find a really nice Linux for
lets 'iustus invenire a nice quod realiter est Linux
me to use in my day to day and when I
in die cum ad me hodie, et
have to do video editing I can reboot
non possum facere reboot video edendis
into Windows 10 right do my video
X dextera mea, video quid in Fenestra
editing in CyberLink PowerDirector which
recensere quae sunt in Cyberlink PowerDirector
performs great and then when I'm done I
magnasque facto deinde ego
switch back into Linux yeah now I've
in yeah nunc switch Linux quia commune aut inmundum
done away with that need to depend on
quod necessitas tollitur dependere
hey I have to be able to do DaVinci
heu tibi esse potero facere DaVinci
Resolve I got it up and going folks so
Cumque surrexissem ea sententia ita fit
if you've got a dreamy computer check
Si tu possedi computatrum reprehendo SOMNICULOSUS
out my blog bald nerd comm do a quick
Nerd calvitium mea blog de facio velox Comm
search for DaVinci Resolve I actually
EGO vere volo quaerere DaVinci
outlined kind of what I went through in
quid autem in specie per delineatur
order to get it up and going
ut pervenit et vado
including the packages that you need to
inter quas necesse est ut packages
install cuz it's a bit onerous so but
sed ut install cuz quod suus 'aliquantulus gravis
it's working as you can see there it's
suus operatus est ut vos can animadverto suus
just complaining that I changed my
sicut mea mutata est et venerunt querentes
resolution because as you know I did
eo consilio feci scitis
that for you so but I'm really impressed
Ego autem in vobis, sed realiter impressa
with Linux Mint okay so let's take away
Bene ergo de Linux Mint et auferent
the need to go with DaVinci Resolve and
cum DaVinci in opus ad quod velis
say all right let's see I was working on
Omnia recte dicis lets 'animadverto opus in me
new every day therefore the week's show
novae igitur quotidie ad spectaculum septimana scriptor
and and that's when I ran out of video
et e, et ut 'quando EGO ran video
memory and everything Linux Mint has is
et omne quod memoria Linux has New
really quite sleek and this looks
satis rem quod spectat mira species et habitudo
exactly like hell MDE I got to admit it
Et prorsus sicut infernum MDE conplexio est quod fateri
does look strikingly similar cinnamon is
hoc manifestius patet respicere similis cinnamomum est,
the menu system it works really well I
Et vere bene operatur enim ea ratio menu
love certain aspects of both lmde and
quaedam facies et amem et lmde
Linux Mint for one I really like the the
Ego vere similis ad in in New unus Linux
navigation I really like the way that it
navigation ita ut EGO vere amo
operates it's just it flows with my kind
suus 'iustus operates est genus fluit meis
of mindset of how the operating system
quomodo questae de operating ratio
in the file system should flow like when
in ut lima ratio influunt, ubi quasi
I plug in a device it gives me access to
Hoc consilium non datur aditus plug in
it the way I think I should have access
Ego sum via, et si accessum habent,
to it and it just seems to work really
et id solum videtur esse opus realiter
really well
bene realiter
I don't really need to go through the
Per me non vere postulo ad
menu and navigation it's all very much
BENE navigationem valde menu
the same as what you've already seen the
Idem iam quid viderim
difference here is that I have things
habeo enim est distinctio
like driver manager and when I bring
exactoris sum sicut procurator ac deducere
that up this is what really makes Linux
hoc est quod vere facit hoc Linux
Mint stand out against lmde
Mentham, et sta in lmde
is because it's based on Ubuntu
secundum quod suus 'quoniam in Ubuntu
it has features like this and they come
Haec features est ut is adveho et
from a boom - so this is like hey if you
ex transuerso - heus sic est ut, si
if you love boom two's capabilities but
Duo autem boom si me diligis, elit scriptor
not boo boom two's interface well Linux
ne boo boom duo interface est Linux bene
Mint really kind of strikes it for you
Re vera Mint percusserit eam alia quaedam ad te
so you can see like my Nvidia card was
sic videre est similis mei card ATI
detected and it just installed and
et compertum quod tantum installed
worked I detected my Broadcom chip and
dicebant pori mihi Broadcom chip quod laboravit
installed and worked so makes things a
installed et facit quae in tam laboravi
lot easier so there are differences but
ut facilius multum divisiones non
they're subtle and they're really user
illi tu es et subtilis re usor
friendly experience kind of things so I
quae sic amica quaedam experientia,
mentioned last week if you're new to
ultimo si vestri 'novus ut octo
Linux go with Linux Mint as opposed to
Linux ire Linux ut opponitur ad New
LMDE because I kind of feel like LMDE is
Quia genus est LMDE sentiant LMDE
a bit more power user ish because of the
aliquantulus magis ob virtutem user introitu
fact that it's not based on your boot -
quod fundatur super tabernus suus 'non -
it's based on Debian you do need to get
suus 'vos postulo impetro secundum debian
your hands kind of a little more dirty
genus paulo manibus sordescere
with that right so I'm kind of thinking
cum me opinioni Habemus
hey I really like this whole thing that
heus ego vere similis hoc quod est totum
the Linux Mint is doing
Linux facit Mint
check out more at Linux Mint com see
Lorem magis com Sede Linux Mint
what you think and if you've got a
et quid tibi videtur, si tu possedi
distro that you really love let me know
distraho quod vere diligit me sciam
and and let me know kind of what you
quae mihi talis ac
think of the idea that maybe we should
quod fortasse debemus cogitare
remove that DaVinci Resolve necessity
necessitas tollere velis DaVinci
from that from that decision and instead
et ex arbitrium ex loco
just find a distro that I really like
Ego vere similis hoc invenire sicut distraho
right
iustum
I mean who knows you might find a
Intelliguntur qui te scit, ut inveniam
district really like that does run da
vere similis da regione non enim curram
Vinci know it says - no because it's not
Vinci scire dicit - hoc nihil est, quia non sunt
no it's not oh right it's actually
suus 'non venias ius non est ipsum
DaVinci Resolve that's saying it don't
DaVinci velis dicere quod non est suus
worry we've got to head over to the
Comperto ad solliciti sunt super caput
newsroom and if you're ready for it I am
et newsroom si vestri 'parata est mihi
I am indeed zip right over all right
Avi omnis jus vero juris sum
here in the stories were covering this
hanc narrationem hic tegebant
week in the category 5 TV newsroom
V TV newsroom septimana ad genus
Bitcoin and other digital currencies
BitCoin et alia digital valūtās
continue to tumble and value admin
et corruisset permanere valorem Administrator
concerns that Wall Street institutions
Wall Street institutions ut de
are shunning cryptocurrencies -
cryptocurrencies declinare -
Madeleine planets wins the british-built
Sainte Britannis signis bene constructum
Aeolus satellite has begun firing its
Aeolum satellite iam inceperat pilas eius
lasers down on earth
Lasers in terra deorsum
a self-driving bus has begun shuttle
ego coepit a pectine bus incessus,
service in Calgary and we may not have
et non ut serviamus Calgary
colonies on Mars and faster than light
Coloniae Martis luminis velocius
travel yet but if you have a Vizio TV
Si adhuc habere nisi iter Vizio TV
you'll get a taste of a bizarre feature
prodigiosum in a pluma youll 'adepto a gustum
wherein gadgets turn against their
turn quibus in suis gadgets
makers after first portraying their
prius artifices eorum effingere
owners also a pop-up informing you that
et pop-sursum owners rescribimus vobis
your TV has been spying on you and will
TV vestri est et voluntatem exploratores provinciae
prompt you to sue its own manufacturer
Opertis ad petendam manufacturer suum
these stories are coming right up
talia sunt usque
don't go anywhere Jeff Westen Gemma
Gemma usquam non Jeff Westen
you're building a brand-new beautiful
tu aedificationem pulchra novum
website what aren't you you're terrible
ne te terribilia quae website
actor what does where acting comes into
Quid in quibus actor agere fiat
play you're supposed to act okay
agere bene vos volo ludere
I'm building a really cool website are
Im 'website sunt, aedificationem a vere frigus
you building a really cool website just
a vere frigus vestri website sicut aedificationem
because Jeff is confused doesn't mean
quoniam confusa est Jeff non sit
you have to be visit cap v dot TV slash
esse tibi dat v visit cap TV VULNUS
dream host to sign up for unlimited web
somniare infinita telam exercitu in signum
hosting for your website with unlimited
pro website hosting habeant cum
email accounts MySQL databases the
email compotis quod MySQL databases
latest version of PHP WordPress and more
tardus poema poematis of WordPress et PHP
and even a free domain name registration
et libera adnotatione domain nomen
it's less than six dollars per month so
minus quam sex pupa per mensis ut suus '
sign up today cat five dot TV slash
dat signum est hodie cattus quinque TV VULNUS
dream host this is the category five dot
host genus hoc somniare dat quinque,
TV newsroom covering the week's top tech
TV scriptor summo tech newsroom covering una sabbatorum
stories with a slight linux bias
pondus exiguum fabulis linux
I'm Sasha Rickman and here the top
Im 'Not Rickman et hic summitatem
stories were following this week Bitcoin
haec sunt sequentes octo fabulas BitCoin
and other digital currencies have
est et alia digital valūtās
continued to tumble in value of mid
continued corruisset est in valore est medium
concerns that Wall Street institutions
Wall Street institutions de illo
are shunning cryptocurrencies it follows
sequitur illud declinare cryptocurrencies
media reports originally in Business
Business primum refert in instrumentis
Insider that American investment bank
Insider ut American investment ripae
Goldman Sachs was shelving plans to set
Ut erat elatae Goldman Sachs consilia
up a crypto currency trading desk
pecuniam a negotiatione Crypto elit
goldman sachs CFO Martin Chavez has
Goldman Sachs CFO Martin habet Chavez
since made publicly clear that the
manifeste patet propositum
reports were false he says I never
nunquam dicit falsum in me tradit
thought I would hear myself use this
exaudi me fore putaverunt ut hanc
term but I really have to describe that
sed vere non est terminus ad describere
news as fake news the truth of the
nuntium nuntium fake quod verum est
matter is Wall Street is loving cryptos
Est Wall Street amantes materia est Crypton
they're even opening an exchange and
erant 'non est commutatio nec atque foramen
Nasdaq is investing in a tool to predict
NASDAQ circumsedere, in hoc instrumentum esse venturam dicunt,
crypto price movements bitcoin has lost
pretium est motus crypto BitCoin amissa
two-thirds of its value in the past nine
duas ex tribus partibus eius valorem, in praeter novem
months it was trading above nineteen
facta est negotiatio novem mensibus
thousand dollars in December and if it
Decembri si centena
continues to fall it could threaten this
incidere posset adhuc minatur
year's low of five thousand eight
humilis octo annorum milia
hundred and eighty seven dollars this
Hoc centena octoginta septem
can affect the value of other coins too
possunt etiam ad valorem aliarum denarios
especially all coins whose value are
quorum nummos omnis valorem maxime qui
based on the value of Bitcoin the future
pretii fundatur super BitCoin de futuro
regulatory framework for digital coins
regulatory compage denarios pro digital
remains unclear in the United States the
incertum manet in Civitatibus Foederatis Americae est
US Securities and the Exchange
Et Exchange Securities US
Commission has warned that some coins
Quem nummos aliquot admonuit ut Commission
might be regarded as securities which
ut qui pro securitate
means dealing in them may become subject
ut in ea re facti est commercium
to federal law according to coin market
coin secundum ad forum foederati legem,
cap the overall market capitalization of
uncialium in foro cap altiore
virtual currencies has lost
virtual valūtās quae amissa
three-quarters of its value since
quarteria, quia ex sua pretii trium
January Peak slumping from eight hundred
January de Pecco octingenti slumping
billion dollars to around two hundred
circiter ducenti billion pupa
billion dollars now blockchain
Nunc billion pupa blockchain
technology enables us to use and
technology, et idoneum ad nos
transact currency quickly safely
cito securus monetæ mors diremit L. Ueturi
interestingly it enables anyone to set
interestingly dat esse alicuius ut
up automated self-employed business
automated auto-administrato negotium sursum
where market where mark contracts will
in qua forum in quo erit signum contractus,
enable vendors to get paid directly by a
enable mercedem recta a ad vendentes,
customer with no middleman you are
Lorem nulla apud vos middleman
already able to create your own currency
iam potuit creare vestri own monetæ
to pay for those services so what's
et quid muneris reddere illis
going wrong here's our crypto
Hic suus 'iens iniuria nostri crypto
correspondent Robert Koenig to share his
Robert correspondent Koenig ad participes eius
thoughts on the state of Bitcoin so
ita cogitat statu BitCoin
what's the reason for this huge drop in
haec causa est quod apud ingens stilla
in market valuation
in foro tanto aestimabitur
from my point of view the main one is
ex parte mea est pelagus
lack of education I've seen so many
et vidi de educatione tot indigentiam
people in this market that have got no
qui ut in hoc foro non habeo
clue what they're talking about a lot of
quid clue erant de multum
youtubers and Twitter also have got an
et in habeo youtubers et Twitter
opinion then are shedding a coin
Effundere ergo nummus videtur
chilling a coin and really don't know
infrigidando atque denarium vere non scitis
what they're talking about many people
quod non erant de multis
don't even understand what the
et quod non intellegis
blockchain is so that's the main reason
id est praecipue blockchain
that a lot of information is in the
qui in hoc multum notitia
market that is false
forum, quod falsum est,
and therefore one has to be very careful
Ergo oportet diligentius
and listening exactly where the news is
et audire non exacte ubi nuntium
coming from even big magazines and news
et ex magnis nuntium horrea bellique
outlets bringing out news that are not
cum eduxeris quæ non sunt nuntium decursibus
correct the other hand is there's also
et corrigere Contra est scriptor
no real use case or mass adoption in
re ipsa et non usu, aut mole in adoption
this crypto market it's an early stage
forum hoc crypto suus gradu praematuro
if you look at Bitcoin it's still at
si illud usque ad intueri BitCoin
version zero point
versio nullus punctus
so it's not version one we're still some
ita non aliquis poema adhuc unum sumus
time away of many people being able to
multi temporis sublatam esse poterat
use or even invest into into cryptos if
uti in, placerat nec vel si in Crypton
we look at who is participating in the
at qui nos participes effecti
market it's really probably less than 1%
foro est minus quam verisimile vere% I
globally people that can participate or
qui aut homines participate globally
are currently participating in this
participating in currently sunt
market there is some manipulation
forum est manipulation aliquam
happening because it's not regulated its
quod fieri non ordinavit sua suus '
global there is manipulation happening
manipulation eveniunt est global
and so that's why there's a reason the
et ideo ratio non est ad
price to drop or go up the market is
ad stillabunt pretium est et ut in foro
really bullish not from the financial
non gerit estque in re pecuniaria
point of view but from the outlook of
sed ex parte mentis est
where cryptocurrencies are going to be
ubi ire ad cryptocurrencies
in a few years time it's going to be
paucis diebus in futurum
huge market that's probably got even
venalicium ut suus 'got ingens quidem verisimile
guaranteed that that's big every big
omne magnum confirmat; quod est magnum
company every financial institution is
omnis financial institutione turba est
looking into this year participating and
aspiciens in participating et hoc anno,
doing something the just from the
sicut enim facientes aliqua ex
logical point of view it is going to be
ad esse rationis illud visum est:
huge so there is nothing to fear from
nihil tam magnum metuendum
the basics basis of cryptocurrencies
et ex basics cryptocurrencies
coming into that I received two
et venient in accepi duo
questions that I'd like to answer which
Ad quod respondendum youd 'amo ut Quaestiones
go in sync with what I just said I mean
per quae intelliguntur sicut dixit mihi vade in sync
Sean asked for example how can I
Saint eg rogavit quid potes me
participate now Sean there
Saint illic participare nunc
aspects of this one is investing yeah so
Hoc est unum et facies circumsedent yeah
and this is not financial advice this is
et haec non est financial consilium
just my my point of view on how I see
sicut me videtis qualiter me in parte
the situation if you want to invest in
situ vis nisi in diam voluptua
this market probably it's a good time to
hoc foro non est tempus bonum est verisimile
do it now the price went down from
quanti autem facere descendit
20,000 to now let's say around 6,000 it
Et circa 6,000 20,000 hactenus lets 'narro
can go a little bit further down there
Praeterea potest, ut exigua ibi
are some people saying it can go down to
sunt aliqui possunt ire ad eum dicens
5,000 but we're just not a huge drop
Sed iustus a ingens 5,000 stilla
from the risk-taking point of view you
ex parte autem periculi-taking
can't even wait a few months a few weeks
nec exspectandum aliquot menses aliquot septimanas
before you invest but it's a good point
sed etiam circum illud bonum est coram te
you know to start investing into Kryptos
circumsedere, in Kryptos scitis incipere
the other one how I can participate is
altera autem quomodo possum participare est
from the programming now that is really
ex programming nunc est realiter
attractive
gratus
there is a huge downside or there's a
downside est ingens et illic 'a
huge market opportunity for programmers
ingens foro occasio programmers
and I would definitely if you know if
et si certa esset, si nosti
you're if you're if you like to program
si tu es, si vis PROGRAMMA
I would definitely go into this market
EGO esset certus ut in hoc foro
and start learning how to program in a
atque doctrina quam ad propositum in incipere
OS e theorem and so on and the other one
Ita et alterum theorema e OS
is for those people that want to build
qui volunt facere ut sit in illis,
something first recommendation is learn
Prima sententia est scire aliquid,
about blockchain yeah if you don't know
de blockchain yeah, si nescis
what blockchain is don't touch it and
et nolite tangere quæ est blockchain
then start dreaming about applications
tum satus applications somnias
that would be new so that there's no
quod novus ut illic 'nulla esset,
case out there and where you can really
qua ex periculo est, et vere potes
change something in your environment or
in environment aliquid immutare uel
in the bigger picture and start building
et maior picture satus ad aedificationem
something it's it's not that difficult
non enim est aliquid, quod suus 'difficile
and the next question is Michael he
altera quaestio est, et quod Michael
asked I heard that the issues of concern
audivi quod de interrogavit de exitibus
around cryptocurrencies including
circum inter cryptocurrencies
potential money laundering and and
et in pecunia lavare potentiale, et
market manipulation well Michael yes
Michael quod sic tam foro manipulation
market manipulation yes that's there and
et sic quod inde forum manipulation
all the big like SEC and so on they're
SEC omnia magna sicut et tu super eos
looking into this year and they will
et erit in quaeritis huius anni
find those that are manipulating the
invenies ea quae sunt deformetur
market and they will be penalized I'm
et in forum ego Socium mulctandum
pretty sure about that the potential of
De pulchellus certus est potentiale
money laundering that is not there that
qui pecuniam lavare non
is just a myth it's much easier to
quanto facilius est, fabula est ut suus '
launder money with US dollars or
launder pecuniam in US pupa vel
Canadian dollars or yours then
Canadian pupa vel tuas et
with cryptocurrencies and why because
quid cum eo cryptocurrencies
the cryptocurrency stays on a blockchain
qui manet in cryptocurrency blockchain
and therefore you can always go back to
ideoque reverti possunt
any transaction that was made and really
quod aliquod factum, et rem
find out what happened
explorare poterimus
yeah with US dollars you can't once
US pupa cum yeah non semel,
they're spent they're gone blockchain
ipsi erant 'spent ipsi erant' recessit blockchain
it's there you can still find in Bitcoin
tamen suus 'non potes reperire in BitCoin
for example the first transaction that
exempli gratia ut primo transaction
was made by Satoshi Nakamoto back in
facta in satoshi Nakamoto
2009 that is there you can see it and so
MMIX id est vos can videre illam et
I cannot recommend doing any money
Pecuniam facere nequeo laudare
laundering or any criminal activities on
aut quis lavare criminalibus actiones in
a blockchain because it will be visible
et quod sic erit visibilis blockchain
and also the government knows who's
et quis scit imperium
participating where because companies
nam societates ibi participating
like coinbase have to report and you can
et non potest referre qualis coinbase
see what public key is linked to what
palam videantur quae de illis quae clavis est coniunctum
name and so you can track the person the
et ideo potest ad track hominem nominare,
the activities of a person in regards to
et ab actionibus &amp; ad hominem
cryptocurrencies now there is of course
nunc utique cryptocurrencies
those privacy coins like Manero and G
quae g Manero signatos uti secreto
cash and so on that we're not allow you
Non sinet ita ut pecuniam
to do that at the moment so I would not
noluit facere ut simul
bank on that so I don't see that as a
ita ut pro ripa non
potential money laundering thing that
qui pecuniam lavare aliquid potentiale
that's just something that is out there
id quod iustum est, quia non sunt
in the market but it's not really an
In foro nisi quod suus 'non realiter
issue and will never be an issue because
quod non potest esse, quia exitus normam
cash will always be a better tool to do
cash est semper esse melius tool ut faciam
these things right that's it that's it
quod non est conveniens quod haec
for me here and back to the studio thank
hic et in me studio laudis
you thank you Robert the british-built
Robert gratias British constructum tecum est
lis satellite has begun firing its
iam inceperat aelis satellite incendii eius
lasers down on earth to map the planets
terris sidera LASERS map
winds it's a big moment for the European
Minimum: magnus est enim Europae momentum
Space Agency mission as the technology
Agency spatium ut technology missio
took 16 years to develop launched three
Tulit XVI annis tribus develop launched
weeks ago from the Kouros space
a hebdomades ago spatio Sententiae
spaceport in French Guiana a Ola Aeolus
Hi enim aeoli pilae spaceport in Guiana
is now undergoing three months of
Nunc de tribus mensibus poenam sustinentes
testing once this is complete scientists
Hoc experimento docti perfecta
will start assessing the satellites wind
incipiet contrariam vapori deposuit satellitibus venti
data for inclusion in weather models its
data ad exempla monstrabit inclusion in tempestate eius
maps are expected to bring significant
maps expectata significant to bring
improvement in the
in melius
see of medium range forecasts those that
mediae range futura praenoscere videre illos qui
look a few days ahead mark dr. mark
ante paucos dies vide notare arcu. marcam
Drinkwater who heads the agency's earth
Drinkwater ad propellente qui principes terræ scriptor
and missions science division says it's
et scientiam missionibus suus 'inquit division
a euphoric feeling in a proud moment to
affectum tempore ad a euphoric in superbus
reach this milestone after overcoming
deposita Hunc lapidem
the first technical challenge to build
provocatione aedificare primum technica
launch and operate this complex wind
ventus launch, et operate universa haec
lidar now we're arguably some of what
Nunc Lidar sumus pars quæ arguably
are arguably some of Europe's most
pars maxima in Europa autem arguably
patients and and scientists and weather
et aegris, et scientists et tempestatis
service services eerily wait to take
ad ministerium cultus expectare eerily
over the baton at the moment when the
dum ibidem super baculum
data comes from multiple but patchy
notitia est ex varius sed multa
sources such as weather blends Aeolus
Aeolus insanis tempestatibus sicut fontes carpens,
will be the first system to gather wind
primum ratio est ventum erit colligentes
information all across the globe from
notitia ex omni trans globe
the ground up to nearly 30 kilometers in
chiliometrorum in terram usque ad fere XXX
altitude it will do this by firing a
altitudo enim est autem hoc per ardendu
powerful ultraviolet laser down into the
Laser ultraviolet in fortitudine
atmosphere with the aid of a telescope
ope aeris telescopio
and a sensitive detector it will then
et in sensitivo ita iucundioris fructum detector
look for the way the pulsed beams light
radii lucis puIsed modo quaerere
is scattered back off the air molecules
qui non est aspergatur retro off caeli moleculis
water droplets and dust particles this
stillæ pulvis particularum haec
should reveal basic details about air
de basic Details caeli sit revelare
movement and numerical weather models
caeli motus exempla monstrabit, et numero
will be adjusted to take account of it
et ob hoc ut esset,
experts confirm that the lasers first
periti primum confirmet lasers
days of working revealed clear features
diebus manifesta features operandi
of the wind I love that they're able to
de vento es amo esse poterit
use lidar as a technology to do this
ut Lidar utuntur hoc technology est
like the same thing that makes
facit ut idipsum
autonomous vehicles possible right and I
et sui iuris, de jure poterit vehicles
mean we I think my basic knowledge of
Ego basic scientia autem meum mean
lidar comes from an interview we did yes
Ita fecit ex colloquio Lidar nos
and we were looking at the the city of
petebant et in civitatem
the monkey god great and with that they
Simia quoniam Deus magnus et
used lidar from an airplane to be able
Lidar usus potest esse ex scapha
to see through the jungle cover into the
ut per operculum in saltu,
into like ruins right so now they're
ut tu nunc in dextrum, sicut in ruinas
using lidar from the sky down and
et per Lidar de caelo
looking at wind patterns which a a
aspiciens in ventum patterns quo aa
medium-range weather forecast with
Providemus tempestate tecum medium-range
accuracy would be amazing and now
et nunc accuracy esset mirabile
there'd be no more jokes left on earth
amplius digereret superstes iocis
because pretty much every joke is about
iocus est quia fere omnes
how bad weather forecasts are it's true
quomodo verum est quod praedicta tempestatibus
but it is annoying yeah so if they can
sed possunt sic memini molestiae
improve they can improve
meliorem possunt amplio
I'm game they'll be happy so I thought
Sum quod eris felix ludum et cogitavi
to myself like is lidar like ultraviolet
placet mihi ut ultraviolet Lidar
laser rays that are streaming down to
ut effusis ad laser radios non
earth is that gonna grow bot brains is
terra infecta cerebro, quod agnus sit crescere bot
that gonna be a problem
agnus dei esse, ut a forsit
so I'd like cancer-causing elements well
et cancer-causando te velis elementa bene
I was thinking I didn't know either so I
Vel sic cogitabam nesciebam
was thinking more like along the lines
quasi per versus cogitabat
if what's it gonna do to people
si ea laudibus? quid est hominibus
let not people what's it gonna do to
plebs at quid est hoc facies, ut non sit amet
life that isn't people right like please
vita, quae non est iustum ut sis populus
pretty fast
pulchellus ieiunium
yeah lidar is a very passive technology
Yeah passiva elit ipsum Lidar
yeah it's completely safe I was I was
Ego sum eam memini tutissimum
looking it up just to see it like
eam iustus vultus amo ut suus
ultraviolet light already exists right
ultraviolet lumen rectis praeexistente
so if you concentrate it a little bit
Si id parum conducunt
what's gonna happen well all plants and
O quid evenire omnibus plantis
animals that are hanging out in the
sunt animalia quae in tentorium
atmosphere I already have their own
Ego iam in sua atmosphaera
natural sunscreen I guess UV sunscreen
Suspicor naturalis sunscreen UV sunscreen
solace in the atmosphere do we need to
non enim est opus in atmosphaera pro solaciis
wear like SPF what we need nothing
SPF gerunt tamquam ea quae nihil opus
nothing we're good we're just we've got
quod nos boni sumus sicut Comperto
we just take advantage of the fact that
hoc solum adfligere quod
we'll know when it's gonna be sunny out
quia cum serenum de te ut suus 'agnus dei esse
we know to put on SPF 60 and I mean in
scimus SPF LX; ego autem dico ad induendum
this day and age like the weather
et quasi tempestas aetate hodie
patterns have been kind of crazy and
exemplarium fuisse quasi insanire
unpredictable right now there's some
inaestimabile nunc illic 'aliquid
storms going on and and I just think if
et si iustus cogitare quod agatur procellas
we can get just really as specific as
sicut vere est ac propria non possumus accipere
possible we can really it's it's a
fieri potest, ut quod suus 'vere non a
safety thing really more than anything
realiter saluti potius
for it can be absolutely there are times
illum esse omnino non sunt tempora,
when it is a safety thing and we we
quod et nos cum salus
certainly feel that right now
quod sentio certe nunc
exactly so very cool an autonomous
ita prorsus sui iuris valde refrigescant
vehicle billed as the future of
billed pro vehiculum posterum
Transportation is spending the month
Translationem exigens mensis
ferrying passengers between two
puellae vector inter duos viatores
neighboring tourist attractions in
propinquae urbis attractionibus
Calgary Alberta
Calgary Alberta
the autonomous electric bus is named
bus nominatur sui iuris, de electrica
Ella and it stands for electronic
Ellam per quem intelligimus electronic
automation and Saturday marked its
Automation et Saturni notatum eius
maiden voyage
virgo navigatione
between the Calgary Zoo and the Telus
Exo inter Calgary et Telus
sparks Science Center next door it can
Science Center scintillas quasdam iuxta ostium potest
carry up to 12 people at a time and it's
ad plebem ferrent hora XII suus
speed has been limited to 12 kilometres
limited celeritate iam ad XII chiliometrorum
an hour for its short journeys between
ad horam paruis itineribus inter
the zoo and the Science Centre Ella runs
et saeptum ferarum Science Center decurrit Ella
on two key technologies Josephine's hang
Suspendisse duobus clavis technologiae Vivamus scriptor
of Telus Park describes one as a super
Super ex Telus Park describitur unus est
fancy version of a GPS and the other is
GPS, et alia version de ludo mentis
wide are short for light detects a
wide sunt brevis lux enim detegit,
detection and ranging which is used to
vndique deprehensio et quae solebat,
detect pedestrians
pedestres deprehendere
or other obstacles in the vehicles path
vehicles in aliisve admotis obstaculis impedita semita
Telus Park is one of the two companies
Park est Telus est duas societates
sponsoring Ellis time in Calgary along
per Eliam in Sponsoring calgary
with energy giant ATCO the federal
Cum industria ATCO foederati giant
government has also put a $50,000 grant
Imperium habet $ 50.000 et posuit præsta
toward the project the vehicle is being
vehiculum quod consilium in
billed as the first electronic
billed sicut primum electronic
autonomous shuttle in Canada able to be
pectine sui iuris, potest esse in Canada,
used as by the public manufacturer easy
usus est facilis in publicam manufacturer
mile at members of the public board a
mille conscendit in membra a publico
similar vehicle in Montreal last year
Suspendisse similis Vehiculum in annum
but that vehicle stayed on the Olympic
lorem nisi qui mansit in Olympiae
Park property Allis presence in Calgary
Vesalius coram Calgary res parco
isn't only about showing off the
Non solum off ad ostendendum
emerging technology of autonomous
emergentes technology autonomi
vehicles researchers are watching to see
Inquisitores vehicles es vigilantes videre
how Ella performs on the gravel roadways
quam Ella viis performs in calculo
linking the zoo in the Science Center
vinculum inter Science Center est in saepti ferarum
and the University of Calgary students
et ex Calgary University alumni
are studying the passengers reaction to
studeo sunt in viatores ad reactionem
the vehicle while there might not be
vehiculum dum ne
anybody controlling Ella directly as it
continuit aliorum directe quasi Ella
makes its trips back and forth there is
et reversus est itinera fecit
a backup system in case emergency human
si tergum est subitis humani systema
intervention is needed saying said there
interventus opus est sermo ait:
is an operator on the bus to make sure
an sit in operator bus fac
everything is running smoothly the
nonumy enim omnia in
vehicle will spend September in Calgary
expendas in vehiculum Septembris Calgary
before moving to Edmonton next month
ut prius motabilem proximo mense Edmonton
so the technology is actually happening
ut nulla omnino fieri
yeah it's there it's real it's it's I
yeah suus 'non ut suus' suus 'suus' realis,
just again about lidar it's it's it's
rursus circa illud quod suus 'iustus est Lidar
literally everywhere now I just I love
Nunc ad literam sum iustus amo undique
the fistic ated type but let me lidar
sed genus fistic consociet onmes in me Lidar
kind of alludes to radar right right you
vox quaedam commemorat ligula iure
know send a signal receive it back send
Mitte mittere signum scio reciperes
a signal receive it back but it's so
sed tam insignem reciperes
detailed right it's so precise like if
Si iustum est ut singula accurato
you think about dots per inch and in
et non cogitare de punctis per inch
terms of like imagery right it's so
sicut ex imaginibus suus dexteram
clear it's so it can make out things
suus manifestum, ut ex hoc possit facere quae
like a human form a pedestrian and
et quasi uiator hominem forment
things like that so I was thinking now
Nunc ut puta cogitationem
I'm a little VR obsessed as we might
Parvulus sum obsessi possemus VR
realize he's a human intervention why is
quid est enim a animadverto interventu
a VR headset now all of a sudden she's
VR tincidunt nunc autem subito ex omnibus quæ scriptor
obsessed obsessed
sapien sapien
so the VR aspect of this that I was
sic in hac me VR
thinking is we probably don't actually
non est autem verisimile cogitandi actually
need a human operator to be honest with
operator humanum opus esse honestiori
you you think we need a VR headset we
VR tu putas, non opus est ut tincidunt
need somebody at a at a central hub that
aliquem ad opus, ut ad a central hub
can control many and just slip with VR
VR control multorum: et non tantum cum lapsum
to the actual bus and be able to
Et potest esse in re bus
actually control
actually control
sounds so sci-fi we don't know it's
sic sonat sci-fi enim non est
person there you know what's coming
nosti quod homo est suus coming
everything that we're talking about ten
quae quia erant de decem
years ago I would have said that sounds
Et sonitus annos esset dixit
so fine now right right but this is real
haec ipsa tam sunt exquisitae, nisi iure iam dextro
this is real so when will that become
haec vera quae ita fiet, cum erit
real when will the avatars become
quando vera avatars facti sunt
reality we actually need a real person
re vera homini de facto opus sit
in there also funny little side note is
inde etiam est paulatim nota quod in ridiculam
the fact that they picked those two
quod illae binae tulerunt
locations in a city in Canada because
locus, in civitatem: quoniam in Canada,
it's a gravel road yes it's a corduroy
Etiam a calculo via suus corduroy
road up there in Canada on the west
illic a via in Canada plagam
coast of Canada there's a corduroy road
maritimum iter corduroy elit illic '
connecting the zoo and whatever and
iunctis et quidquid ferarum
they're right next door so it doesn't
tu non recta tunc ianua ut non
have to go far yeah also side note they
Ave maris et procul ire cantu
call it the easy mile the company's
facile dixerim dolor passuum
called easy mile I get it but we're in
faciles dicuntur mille et pervenit autem in nobis es
Canada now it's an easy kilometre easy
Nunc facile est kilometre blandit facilisis
2.6 kilometers that's right something
2.6 chiliometrorum eo iustum est aliquid,
like that we may not have calling these
quod, sicut potest non vocant isti
on Mars and faster than the light to
celeris Martis lux
travel yet but if you have a Vizio TV
iter autem si tamen habes in TV Vizio
you will get a taste of a bizarre
prodigiosum in a eris gustum
feature where gadgets turn against their
turn in eorum pluma ubi gadgets
makers after first betraying their
prius proditionibus fabros
owners also a pop-up informing you that
owners et pop-sursum rescribimus vobis
your TV has been spying on you will
Suspendisse vestri TV est in vobis erit
prompt you to sue its own manufacturer
Opertis ad petendam manufacturer suum
all this gadget drama started on
drama coepi super omne gadget
November 2015 when journalistic watchdog
November MMXV cum journalistic watchdog
Pro Publica
Pro Publica
exposed Vizio for illegally using its
et legem ejus per patere Vizio
popular Smart TVs to spy on its
popularibus smart TV misit Iudas speculari eius
customers the secret feature recorded
pluma secretum memoriae customers
what when and where it's TV users were
quando et ubi quid TV suus 'users sunt
watching in order to sell their viewing
vigilantes in ut vendere viewing
habits data to advertisers then
ergo habitum advertisers data est
advertised advertisers could use that
proscriptis advertisers posse uti, quod
data to find you on your phone and other
et alia tui invenire notitia super vestri telephonum
devices and target your you with your
et vos cum target cogitationum vestrarum
advertisements tailored to those habits
About Me habitum discriminatim pro ea
pretty sleazy the company argued that it
satis lubricam societatis ut ad
was innocent and that all data recording
et universa quæ data est memoria innocentes
was anonymous and not specific to each
anonymous non est propria unicuique
user and asked the class-action lawsuit
et rogavit iudicium user classis actio,
to be dismissed but a California federal
ut tamen dimisit a foederati California
judge didn't buy its arguments two times
buy iudicet et non ad rationes duo tempora
in March and July allowing the legal
et in iure Martio Iulii permittens
process to can
processus ut can
this was despite the fact that in
et in hoc non obstante,
February 2017 the company came to a very
February MMXVII factum est societas in ipso
friendly 2.2 million dollar settlement
amica, 2.2 million pupa sedes
with the FTC on this investigation as
cum hac FTC inquirunt
part of the legal process against the
pars legalis in processus
company I'd agreed to push a notice to
Id 'constat a comitatu ad ventilabis ad notitiam
all affected Smart TVs alerting
Smert TV alerting omnes affectus
consumers of what happened and what
et quid sint occae consumers
their rights are the notice should show
eorum iura esse debet notitiam et ostendam
up sometime between September 12th and
September 12th inter usque nunc
October 3rd now more than ever if you
3 Octobris nunc plus umquam nisi
are a Vizio Smart TV owner stay tuned
Smert TV dominus maneat versa sunt Vizio
what kind of TV do you have I have a
id quod habetis habeo enim quaedam TV
Panasonic okay yes Panasonic B I
Casio Casio bene B ita ut
remember because when the washing
recordare quia lavacrum
machines were blowing up or whatever it
et quidquid machinae agitari
was I was really worried yeah yeah this
ego anxius eram vere yeah hoc yeah
could like be any moment I'm looking at
est sicut quis non tempore ad me?
the calendar hearing today when we're
in calendar ubi auditus sumus hodie,
filming this episode is the 12th so you
hoc est, filming Episode 12 ita et vos
may be watching this on your Vizio TV
potest haec vigilantes TV super Vizio
and suddenly there's that pop-up pop-up
et subito ad pop sursum pop-
right which they would do because they
quia iure facturos
would know that you're watching category
Scio tibi esse vigilantes genus
five and you would immediately close it
et statim claudet eam quinque
ignoring the pop-up because you want to
quia unica evadit et pop-sursum vis
watch the show right so it's strategy
Itaque iure spectabant consilium
right
iustum
artificial intelligence they've got they
Ive 'got hi artificialis intelligentia,
know exactly what you're watching Voight
scis exacte voluisti vigilantes Voight
getting in trouble right interesting
questus est in dextera tribulationis interesting
right I mean we talk about future
vult enim me futurum recte loqui
technology and thinking that okay well
Accumsan Lorem arbitratus satis
what would happen if robots suddenly you
quid si robots repente
know went through a lawsuit because
et quod per causam cognoscere
they're monitoring what happens if Alexa
ipsi erant 'Alexa si vigilantia fit
I'm sorry oh I keep doing that and then
Paenitet heu mihi, ut et observabitis caerimonias istas
now every Alexa everywhere is like
Omnis undique simile Alexa
canceled
remittantur
we're cool my babies YouTube we're cool
sumus infantes meos frigus frigus YouTube sumus
YouTube I don't want to hear about it
YouTube non volunt audire de illa
true story
fabula vera
yeah what like what what happens legal
yeah, quae placet, quod fit legal
it happens if right yeah and and then
et tum forte fas Yeah
what are the ramifications and what does
et quod ramificationes quid facit,
that do for for the services because if
Quod si quid est ad quod muneris
it's deemed that hey if we develop a
ut habetur quod si suus 'heus develop a
service that does what these devices
servitium faciant cogitationes
which I'm not going to say the word
Im 'non iens ut, qui dicit verbum
because I caught myself what if these
Quid si ego deprensus sum
devices are monitoring our every speech
voce magna in omni cogitatu
and things and
et quae sunt, et
now we can't we can't create the product
iam non possimus, non possumus creare productum
that people want to be able to ask it
volo petere est quod possit
for the weather and the cookie recipes
et propter tempestatem crustulum mixturis
and things like that mm-hmm
et huiusmodi mm hmm,
and so what if we can't manufacture that
quod efficere potest ut si
because we're gonna get sued right there
erant 'agnus dei adepto est, quod sequitur rectam
comes a point I guess what it comes down
EGO coniecto quod in parte sua venit et ita fit
to I guess where I would have to stop
EGO coniecto ut ubi volo ut prohibere
the that trail of thought and say okay
illo trahentium in bene cogitandi regulas tradit et dicere
where this is different is that Vizio
ubi est alia est Vizio
didn't disclose this to their writers
non ipsorum Cardinalium scriptores
when I buy an echo you know I did that I
scio ubi sum ego et vos emere resonare
know what I'm getting myself into I know
in questus scio me scire, quid me
that she's listening right when I
quod audire fas cum illa
finally write so so is that there is
tandem, quod ita sit ut scribunt
that my opt-in is that my approval of
quia mea est, ut optet-in of meus approbatione
okay I understand that if I'm watching
si bene intelligo quia vigilabo
category five and the host messes up
partibus quinque in genere militiae
then I'm probably gonna order a
Ego igitur quo verisimile est agnus
dollhouse
dollhouse
I here's the thing though I think that
Quod puto quamquam res hic mihi est
it's not about the collection of the
non illam quae est collectum per circuitum
information I assume that there is a lot
notitia est Pono ut multum
of my privacy
secretum meum
that I is that I expect is private but
non enim est occultum quod expecto
it's not private like I expect that when
Non puto quod simile privato est
I'm in my living room having a
Im 'non habens in exedra
conversation with the devices around me
conversationem cogitationes apud circum me,
probably they're absorbing some of that
ut probabiliter absorbuit erant quaedam illius
conversation that I'm actually pretty
ut Im 'pulchellus conversationem actually
okay with it's the selling it to
vendere sibi bene cum ea eam
somebody else that I'm not okay with but
Im 'non bene, sed non apud aliquem alium
if it's are we coming into a world
Si enim non est venturus est in mundum
though Sasha we're like because when I'm
quia etsi Not sumus ut ubi sum
on my computer and I'm looking around
a me PC circuitu me?
suddenly I start getting ads for things
Ads satus questus ea repente
that oh my goodness I really want that
heu mihi quia ego vere volo ut bonitatem
that's so me that's what I've been
quod suus me, quam quod suus 'Ego fui
looking for right right so if I'm having
Im 'vultus pro iure ius habent ut, si
a conversation with my wife and it's a
uxor mea et colloquium cum a
private conversation and in it's being
et in occulto essentiae
recorded anonymously in such a way that
ita memoriae anonymo in ea
it's really just picking up on keywords
Arreptisque suus 'vere iustus super keywords
and trash and kind of it's making a kind
ut quoddam genus nugas et suus
of a picture of what kinds of things I
picturae genera rerum quae
like right if I have particular
sicut iustum est, si particular
political views or if I'm interested in
Im 'interested in publicam vel
certain technologies if I come home and
et si venerit domum cujusdam technologiae
tell my wife about how excited I am
uxor mea dic mihi quomodo concitatae
about the rock pro 64 and then suddenly
repente in LXIV fortis pro
I start seeing advertisements for oh
O advertisements pro me satus seeing
they've got a case for it right oh you
non enim fas O vos Ive 'got a casu,
know that's where the technology has to
scio ubi suus technology habet
go it's it's true I mean I I know that
ire suus 'verum, quod sit non scire II
there are some people who are kind of up
Sunt et quaedam sunt
in arms about having a conversation
armis habens colloquium
about something and then seeing
et cum aliquid de
advertisements for it you know days
About Me scitis quia diebus
later somewhat I feel I feel yeah but
post aliquantum yeah sed sentio me sentire
other other ways I think it's a bit of
alia alii modi puto suus 'aliquantulus of
selective perception like it it's that
hoc est quod amo sensus electionem selectivam,
you're seeing it now because you talked
quia cum eo iam cupis loquebatur
about it not that you're see like
circa illa quae non videmus, sicut tu
because you're you're more aware because
tu quod es magis propter conscientiam
you've talked about it it was probably
tu verisimile esse loquebatur de illo
already there in some cases do you know
jam in quibusdam casibus non scitis
what I'm saying
quid me dicens
yeah no that the very things I search
yeah, ut nulla res te ipsum quaerere
for are being advertised to Me's right
quia es admonitus ad dextrum mihi est scriptor
the things you search for but not the
sed quia talia sunt, non quaeres
conversations you have not yet right I
Sermones non habetis nondum recte
don't have one of those devices right
qui ius non habent artes
but I I'm not against it I not against
non sum ego, sed adversus eam non in
it and I think that there is that line
atque Esse et illud
where we are opting into the
in quo opting nos
technologies that we are purchasing and
technologiae et quae sunt acquirendi
we're saying hey this is okay I've got
erant 'heus dicens haec Ego got bene
my smartphone I'm using alright
Im 'usura Licuit Mauris quis felis mi
gooble right and see my carry job
gooble meam videre ius et officium gesturum
community and so if I'm using that then
et si ergo me, ut per civitatem
mi opted in - yeah right I have to be
cooptati pariter in mi - yeah habeo iustum esse
okay with what they're using that data
ut quid erant 'usura bene in notitia
for right right so maybe I'm not maybe I
ad dextram et recta me maybe non sum maybe
am I I guess I am I'm like like right
Ego coniecto sicut ego amo iustum sum II
now currently in like obsessed like
ut obsiderentur modo quasi per currently
infatuated with the tell me about my day
o vaecors et cum dicite mihi de me hodie
feature oh sure right give me some good
certa utinam mihi jus pluma aliquo bono
news here what they won't they won't
huc nuntium non enim quod non sunt,
give me there is no good news in Canada
inde est mihi bonum nuntium in Canada,
yes but i but i tell but i ask it to
sed non sic; sed ad eam petere
tell me about my day and the assistant
dicite mihi adiutor meus et hodie
is amazing i love it i know everything
scio te amo mirabile est quia omnia
that's going to happen I know the
Novi quod evenit futurum
weather I know how long it's gonna take
quam diu caeli novi suus 'agnus dei accipere
me to my next thing I am down although
deinde etiamsi in rem meam ad me
the weather better was like we're
et quasi tempestas meliora sumus
unfortunately out of time but please
quod valde dolendum velit nisi ex tempore,
comment below let us know what your
ineo quod permissum nos teneo te deorsum
thoughts are about these kinds of
cogitationes tales sunt
technologies listening eavesdropping
technologiae audire auscultatio
collecting data in order to advertise
colligendis notitia in ordine audire te volui,
to us is it okay is it something that
est aliquid quod est bene nobis
we've opted into with the society that
cooptati pariter apud societatem quae in nos
we live in and the technologies that are
qui vivimus, in et technologiae
around us or is it something that you're
neque est aliquid quod nos circa vestri '
totally uncool with let's comment below
Sint enim prorsus invenusta est scriptor comment inferius
yes
etiam
big thanks to Roy W Nash game fairs and
John W Nash gratias magnus ludo et repleverunt nundinas tuas
our community of viewers for submitting
ex nostro conventu viewers ad submittendum
stories to us this week thanks for
Hoc septimana gratias agens pro fabulis nobis
watching the category-five TV newsroom
Genus vigilantes TV, quinque newsroom
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
Similis est, et nolite oblivisci subscribe
all your tech news with a slight linux'
tech proelio levi facto Linux vester cunctis per nuntium,
bias and for more free content be sure
studium liberos et ultra contentus cave
to check out our website from the
Lorem website ex
category-five TV newsroom I'm Sacha
genus TV quinque-newsroom me Sacha
Rickman Thank You Sasha and I'm Robbie
Tibi gratias ago tibi, et Rickman Not Robbie me
Ferguson it's been such a pleasure
Sic suus 'iam Felix Tacitus
having you here again with us this week
quod hic iterum septem habens nobiscum
and we're looking forward to seeing you
et nos exspecto ut vos
again
rursus
one week from now take care
una autem sabbati ab curet
[Music]
[Musica]